

# **GONZALO CARDOZO**

DATA ANALYST | BI ANALYST

# ABOUT ME

Motivated Data Analyst & Business Intelligence Analyst with experience working with data from a variety of industries. Passionate about BI development, modelling and architecture to build models that resolve business issues. I consider myself enthusiastic and capable of showing optimism and responsibility as part of a team.

### SKILLS

- Power BI
- Python

- SQL
- Seaborn, Matplotlib
- Machine Learning
- Scikit Learn
- Text Mining
- Tableau
- Pandas
- Excel
- Orange
- Dashboarding
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Active Listening
- Negotation
- Proactive
- Critical Thinking

### LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - B1

# CONTACT

- Málaga, Spain
- gonzacard@gmail.com
- +39 3477380244
- in /gonzacard

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Data Scientist - Project**Digital House

05/2022 - 12/2022 Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Trained, implemented and evaluated Machine Learning models using Scikit Learn for a bank credit rating risk system with Python.
- · Used model assembly and boosting.
- Applied data cleaning and manipulation techniques (EDA and ETL).
- Made the model available with the Streamlit library.

**Assistant Manager of Health Insurance Benefits** 07/2018 - 11/2021 **River Plate Adventist Sanitarium & Hospital** Entre Ríos, Argentina

- Prepared reports and dashboards for the manager using the KPIs of the different health insurances in Power BI. Interpreting and identifying where we should focus on price negotiations.
- Automated real time data reporting by implementing SaaS Bl. Reduced the delay times in patient attention in the department.
- Oversaw 25+ people from three separate departments and the different HR strategies within the Medical Benefits management, recruitment and selection, training, communication, and development.

# Data Analyst BI - Project

03/2021 - 07/2021

**Digital House** 

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Used analytical programs for the development of control charts and reports on automotive crime in the city of Buenos Aires with Power BI.
- Applied storytelling, dashboarding and data visualisation techniques with their corresponding KPls.
- Extracted data with MySQL, information architecture concepts and Data Warehouse.
- Implemented different business analysis.

#### ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Assistant Financial Manager (Volunteer)**Maluti Adventist Hospital

11/2021 - 12/2022 Mapoteng, Lesotho

Dean of Student Residences (Volunteer)

07/2017 - 07/2018 Røyse, Norway

2016

Tyrifjord Videregående Skole

# EDUCATION

Data Science - Digital House	2022
Python from Scratch Course - Udemy	2022
Data Analytics - Digital House	2021
Diploma in Capital Market - University of CEMA	2020
Certified Public Accountant - River Plate Adventist Univ.	2017

Bachelor of Business Administration - River Plate Adventist Univ.